Daniel Yankelovich Papers
© 2002 University of Connecticut
- Series IV: Subject Files,1965-1992
  - Public Opinion (International)
    - Polish Center for the Study of Public Opinion, 1988 (Box 83:1916-1918)
  - Race, Poverty, and Urban Problems
    - Department of Psychology, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, Illinois Studies of Economically Disadvantaged, 1971 (Box 83:1919)
    - Gans, Herbert, "The Failure of Urban Renewal: A Critique and Some Proposals", 1965 (Box 83:1920)
    - Gurin, Gerald, Inner-City Negro Youth in a Job Training Project: A Study of Factors Related to Attrition and Job Success, 1968 (Box 83:1921)
    - Moynihan, Daniel P., "Poverty Problems", 1968 (Box 83:1922)
    - Moynihan, Daniel P., "The President and the Negro: The Moment Lost", 1967 (Box 83:1923)
    - Oladipupo, Raymond O., "How Distinct is the Negro Market?",, 1969 (Box 83:1924)
    - Ramsey, Francis W., "A Study of Race Prejudice Above the Mason-Dixon Line", 1969 (Box 83:1925)
    - Reissman, F. and J. Dawkins, Play it Cool in English, 1967 (Box 83:1926)
    - Sarbin, Hershel B., "The Business of Dealing with Poverty": address, 1968 Oct 31 (Box 83:1927)
    - Social and Community Planning Research, 3rd Annual Report, 1972 (Box 83:1928)
    - TIME magazine special issue on Black America, 1970 Apr 6 (Box 83:1929)
    - Trans-action: Social Science and Modern Society, vol. 2 no. 4, 1965 May/Jun (Box 83:1930)
    - White and Negro Attitudes Towards Race Related Issues and Activities - A CBS News Public Opinion Survey, 1968 (Box 83:1931)
    - Wilson, Alan B., "The Consequences of Segregation: Academic Achievement in a Northern Community", 1969 (Box 83:1932)
  - Reference and statistics
    - Catalogs of social science publications, undated, 1972-1973 (Box 83:1933)
    - Flax, Michael J., "A Study in Comparative Urban Indicators: Conditions in 18 Large Metropolitan Areas", 1972 Apr (Box 83:1934)
    - National Science Board, Science Indicators 1982, 1983 (Box 84:1935)
    - Statistical Reporter, nos. 71-3, 71-8, 72-3, 1970-1971 (Box 84:1936)
    - Straley, Walter W., "1. Changing Labor Force 2. Hiring and Training": slide presentation, 1970 May (Box 84:1937)
    - Tables of Contents of Selected Advertising and Marketing Publications, vol. 6, nos. 3-4, 1972 (Box 84:1938)
    - Vital and Health Statistics, series 2 no. 48, series 10, no. 72, 1972 (Box 84:1939)
    - Voluntary Support of Education 1968-69, 1969 (Box 84:1940)
  - Social Indicators
    - General Electric Co., "Our Future Business Environment: Developing Trends and Changing Institutions", 1968 Apr (Box 84:1941)
    - Contril, Albert and Charles Roll, Jr., Hopes and Fears of the American People, 1971 (Box 84:1942)
    - "Center for National Goals and Alternatives": design-study report, 1970 Dec (Box 84:1943)
    - "The Corporate Need to Communicate": slide presentation, undated (Box 84:1944)
    - Educational Policy Research Center, Alternative Futures and Educational Policy, 1970 (Box 84:1945)
    - Heilbroner, Robert L., "The Future of Capitalism", 1966 (Box 84:1946)
    - Kahn, Herman, "Forces for Change in the Final Third of the Twentieth Century": informal discussion, 1970 Mar (Box 84:1947)
    - Kroos, Herman E., "Some Economic Lessons of the Sixties": informal discussion, 1970 Jan (Box 84:1948)
    - Sibson & Co. Inc., "Future Business Environment Relevant to Business Planning and Development", 1969 Oct (Box 84:1949)
    - U.S. Department of Labor, "Six Trends We Must Watch", 1972 Nov (Box 84:1950)
  - Sociology
    - Mechner, Francis, "Behavior Technology and Social Change", 1966 (Box 84:1951)
    - Queens College Children and Parents Center, South Jamaica: A Community Study, 1966 (Box 84:1952)
    - Social Science Research Council newsletters, Items, 1966-1967 (Box 84:1953)
    - Daniel Yankelovich, Inc., Proposal to Provide Expert Evaluators in Areas of Manpower, Education, Housing, Aging, Community Services, Rural Services, and Other Areas of CAP Programs", 1968 (Box 84:1954)
    - Clein, Isidor, "On the Concept of Power", 1969 (Box 85:1955)
    - Bureau of Applied Social Research, "Working Papers of the International Study of Opinion Makers", 1969 Feb (Box 85:1956-1959)
    - Barton, Allen and C. Kadushin, "American Elites and Social Problems: The Processes of Opinion-Making", 1969 May (Box 85:1960)
    - Center for Policy Research articles, 1970-1971 (Box 85:1961)
    - Bureau of Applied Social Research newsletters, 1972 (Box 85:1962)
  - Speeches
    - Gavert, R. V., "Marketing Prerequisites For Tomorrow", 1973 Aug (Box 85:1963)
    - Grigg, Murray, et al, proceedings of Super Market Institute Midwinter Executive Conference, 1973 Jan (Box 85:1964)
    - Kahn, Herman - Krugman, H. E., 1973-1975 (Box 85:1965)
    - Skelly, Florence (vice-president, Daniel Yankelovich, Inc.)
      - "The Effect of Social Trends on Future Products and Services", 1969 (Box 85:1966)
      - "Measuring Public Policy Pressures on Marketers", 1976 (Box 85:1967)
      - Outline of talk for Corporate Communications Seminar, 1976 (Box 85:1968)
  - Statistics files
    - Aid to Nicaragua, 1986 (Box 85:1969)
    - Communism versus U.S. involvement, 1986 (Box 85:1970)
    - Confidence in government, 1978 (Box 85:1971)
    - Daniloff case, 1986 (Box 85:1972)
    - Decline in competitive vitality, 1986 (Box 85:1973)
    - Education, 1978 (Box 85:1974)
    - Foreign policy, 1980, 1986 (Box 85:1975)
    - Iceland nuclear arms summit, 1986 (Box 85:1976)
    - Income, 1980 (Box 85:1977)
    - Libya, 1986 (Box 85:1978)
    - Nuclear arms issues, undated (Box 85:1979)
    - Pre-Iceland nuclear arms summit, 1986 (Box 85:1980)
    - Reagan foreign policy decisions, 1986 (Box 85:1981)
    - Reagan response to terrorist attacks, 1986 (Box 85:1982)
    - Relations with the USSR, 1986 (Box 85:1983)
    - SALT II, 1986 (Box 85:1984)
    - Science and technology, undated (Box 85:1985)
    - Social morality, 1980 (Box 85:1986-1987)
    - South Africa, 1986 (Box 86:1988)
    - Voting and candidate positions, 1986 (Box 86:1989)
    - Work, 1980 (Box 86:1990)
  - Survey Data
    - ABC News/Washington Post polls, 1985 (Box 86:1991)
    - American Council of Education survey of college freshmen, 1985 (Box 86:1992)
    - American Council of Life Insurance and the Health Insurance Association of America, The Baby Boom Generation, 1983 (Box 86:1993)
    - American Council of Life Insurance survey data, 1984 (Box 86:1994)
    - CBS News/New York Times polls, 1981, 1984 (Box 86:1995)
    - Compendium of 1970s survey data, 1970-1979 (Box 86:1996)
    - Democratic Party, "Democrats Poll Report: A Survey of the Political Climate in America and Voter Attitudes Toward the 1982 Elections",, 1982 Jan (Box 86:1997)
    - Eyewitness News/Daily News polls (New York City area), 1985-1986 (Box 86:1998)
    - Gallup polls, 1981-1984 (Box 86:1999)
    - Ladd, E. C., Jr. and S. Lipset, "Public Opinion and Public Policy: The United States in the 1980s", 1980 (Box 86:2000)
    - Los Angeles Times polls, 1985-1986 (Box 86:2001-2002)
    - Louis Harris and Associates, Inc.
      - Outline of survey on environmental issues, 1980 (Box 86:2003)
      - "The Survey of Americans' Attitudes Toward Japan and Japanese People", 1986 (Box 86:2004)
    - NBC News polls, 1981-1986 (Box 86:2005)
    - "Opinion Roundup," in Public Opinion, 1978-1979, 1983 (Box 86:2006)
    - Public Agenda Foundation, "U.S. National Survey Summary Tables" (incomplete), 1982 (Box 86:2007-2008)
    - Roper press release on poll conducted for Virginia Slims concerning roles of American women, 1980 (Box 86:2009)
    - University of Connecticut Roper Center data on social questions, 1980 (Box 86:2010)
    - Yankelovich, Daniel
      - "The Foreign Policy Mandate: Regaining Control Abroad", 1981 (Box 86:2011)
      - "Anti-Soviet Minority Grows Larger", 1983 (Box 86:2012)
    - Yankelovich, Skelly, and White, Inc.
      - "TIME 1980 Election Soundings", 1979 Oct (Box 86:2013)
      - "The Post Iowa TIME Survey", 1980 Jan (Box 86:2014)
      - "The 1980 Presidential Campaign - Midpoint in the Primaries", 1980 Mar (Box 86:2015)
      - "The Impact of the New York and Connecticut Primaries on the Presidential Race", 1980 Apr (Box 87:2016)
      - "The Last of the 1980 TIME/Yankelovich Primary Polls", 1980 May (Box 87:2017)
      - "1980 Presidential Election Campaign - September Reading", 1980 Sep (Box 87:2018)
      - "TIME Soundings: The Reagan Administration - May, 1981", 1981 May (Box 87:2019)
      - "TIME Soundings: The First Nine Months of the Reagan Administration", 1981 Sep (Box 87:2020)
      - "The Reagan Administration - Spring 1982", 1982 Mar (Box 87:2021)
      - "TIME Soundings on Communism", 1983 Jul (Box 87:2022)
      - "TIME Soundings - September, 1983 - Political and Economic Findings", 1983 Sep (Box 87:2023)
      - "December TIME Poll" (upcoming), 1983 Nov (Box 87:2024)
      - Impact of KAL 007 incident on public views of USSR, 1983 Dec (Box 87:2025)
      - "Public Opinion Re the Soviet Union", 1983 Dec (Box 87:2026)
      - "TIME Soundings - December, 1983", 1983 Dec (Box 87:2027)
      - "TIME Soundings - February, 1984", 1984 Feb (Box 87:2028)
      - "TIME Soundings, Findings on Economic Issues", 1984 Feb (Box 87:2029)
      - "Current TIME Sounding Data on Lebanon", 1984 Feb (Box 87:2030)
      - "TIME Soundings - September, 1984", 1984 Sep (Box 87:2031)
      - "TIME Soundings - October, 1984", 1984 Oct (Box 87:2032)
      - "TIME/Yankelovich Poll - July 1985", 1985 Aug (Box 87:2033)
      - "A Fifty-Year Report Card on the Social Security System", 1985 Aug (Box 87:2034)
  - Violence
    - Yankelovich, D., "Economic Frustration Persistent Stepchild of Violent Crime", 1981 (Box 87:2035)
  - Watergate
    - TIME Soundings on Watergate, 1973 (Box 87:2036)
    - Gallup Poll indexes on Watergate, 1973 (Box 88:2037)
    - Harris Polls on Watergate, 1973-1974 (Box 88:2038)
    - Libbey, K. and W. Klecka, "The Election of Tom Luken: How Much Difference Did Watergate Make?", 1974 (Box 88:2039)
    - Garrett, J. and B. Wallace, "Attitudes on Watergate: A Search For Significant Determinants", 1974 (Box 88:2040)
    - Watergate bibliography and partial chronolo, [1974] (Box 88:2041)
    - Garrett, J. and B. Wallace, "Cognitive Consistency, Repression-Sensitization, and Level of Moral Judgment: Reactions to the Watergate Scandal", 1975 (Box 88:2042)
  - Women
    - "Values, Interests, and Life Orientations of American Women", 1958 (Box 88:2043)
    - Louis Harris and Associates, Inc., The 1970 Virginia Slims American Women's Opinion Poll, 1970 (Box 88:2044)
    - Keller, Suzanne, "The Future Status of Women in America", [1972] (Box 88:2045)
    - Carbine, Patricia, "Women in Management", [1972] (Box 88:2046)
    - Louis Harris and Associates, Inc., The 1972 Virginia Slims American Women's Opinion Poll (pocket size edition), 1972 (Box 88:2046)
    - Seifer, Nancy, Absent From the Majority: Working Class Women in America, 1973 (Box 88:2047)
    - Ross, Heather, "Poverty: Women and Children Last", 1973 (Box 88:2048)
    - Sawhill, I., H. Ross, and A. MacIntosh, "The Family in Transition", 1973 (Box 88:2049)
    - Proposal for a study on women's and youth employment, 1974 (Box 88:2050-2051)
    - Roper Organization, Inc., The Virginia Slims American Women's Opinion Poll: Volume III, 1974 (Box 88:2052)
    - Institute for World Order, Inc., "How Women Can Build a More Livable World," in Transition newsletter, 1976 Feb (Box 88:2053)
    - Lee, Barbara, Working Women, 1976 Jul (Box 88:2054)
    - National Women's Conference, National Plan of Action, 1977 (Box 88:2055)
    - Landeau, S. and G. Bailey, The Landeau Strategy: How Working Women Win Top Jobs, 1980 (Box 88:2056-2058)
    - Voices For Women: 1980 Report of the President's Advisory Committee for Women, 1980 (Box 88:2059)
    - Women in the Work Force: A Conference on the Economic and Social Impact of Working Women in the 1980s, 1980 (Box 89:2060)
    - YSW, "Social Values Issues Among Women",, 1981 (Box 89:2061)
    - YSW, "Supermarket Shoppers in a Difficult Economic Environment" - draft, 1982 (Box 89:2062-2063)
    - Lein, L. and L. O'Donnell, "The Mainstream Woman: A New Voice in American Politics",, 1984 (Box 89:2064)
  - Youth
    - Daniel Yankelovich, Inc., Profile of a Generation, 1969 Apr (Box 89:2065-2068)
    - Daniel Yankelovich, Inc., Changing Youth Values in the Seventies: A Study of American Youth - Summary Report, 1974 Mar (Box 89:2069-2074)
    - Daniel Yankelovich, Inc., Changing Youth Values in the 70's: A Study of American Youth (condensed version and background material), 1974 (Box 89:2075)
- Series V: Related Material,1959-1991
  - Books
    - Alphandery, Claude, Les Structures D'Insertion Par L'Economique, 1990 (Box 90:2076)
    - Campbell, Angus, The Sense of Well-Being in America: Recent Patterns and Trends - uncorrected proof, 1980 (Box 90:2077)
    - Etzioni, Amitai, An Immodest Agenda: Rebuilding America Before the 21st Century (photocopy), 1983 (Box 90:2078-2082)
    - Federal Communications Commission, The Law of Political Broadcasting and Cablecasting: A Political Primer, 1984 (Box 90:2083)
    - Ford Foundation Project on Social Welfare and the American Future, The Common Good: Social Welfare and the American Future, 1989 (Box 90:2084)
    - Kondrashov, Stanislav, The Life and Death of Martin Luther King, 1981 (Box 90:2085)
    - National Advisory Council on Economic Opportunity, Critical Choices for the 80's, 1980 (Box 90:2086)
    - Pechman, Joseph, ed., Options for Tax Reform, 1984 (Box 90:2087)
    - Report of the Presidential Commission on Aviation Security and Terrorism, 1990 (Box 90:2088)
    - Committee for Economic Development, Productivity Policy: Key to the Nation's Economic Future, 1983 (Box 90:2089)
    - Siberman, Mickey, untitled psychology dissertation draft, undated (Box 91:2090-2091)
  - Conferences
    - "Cost vs. Healthcare: America's Healthcare Dilemma": transcript of public affairs conference, 1985 Mar (Box 91:2092)
    - Donald S. McNaughton Symposium, "Informing America: Who is Responsible?", 1985 Apr (Box 91:2093)
    - Ford Foundation Conference, 1984 May (Box 91:2094)
    - Proceedings of the Third Annual Conference of the Association for Consumer Research, 1972 (Box 91:2095)
    - "The Role of the Press in Democratic Revitalization," discussion group, 1990 Dec (Box 91:2096)
    - Symposium on American Voter Participation, 1983 Sep (Box 91:2097)
    - Universitat Bremen Discussion Group, 1991 Mar (Box 91:2098)
    - Wharton/Reliance Symposium, 1991 Mar (Box 91:2099)
  - The Connecticut Mutual Life Report on American Values in the 80's: The Impact of Belief - information packet, 1981 (Box 91:2100-2101)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1992 (Box 91:2102)
  - Financial Reports (public)
    - U.S. West, Inc. and U.S. Capital Funding, Inc. (Box 91:2103)
  - Interviews
    - Christian Science Monitor interview: audio tape, undated (Box 92:2104)
    - MacNeil-Lehrer affirmative action interview: preparation material, 1991 May 20 (Box 92:2105-2108)
    - Public Opinion interview: transcript, 1987 Oct 14 (Box 92:2109)
    - Werner Erhard interview: correspondence, 1987 May 9 (Box 92:2110)
  - Journal Issues
    - AGB Reports, Journal of the Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, 1983 May/Jun (Box 92:2111)
    - American Demographics, Dow Jones & Company, Inc., 1986 Apr (Box 92:2112)
    - American Renewal, Time, Inc., 1981 (Box 92:2113)
    - The Annals, American Academy of Political and Social Science, "The Energy Crisis: Reality or Myth", vol. 410, 1973 Nov (Box 92:2114)
    - Arms Control Today, 1986 Jan/Feb (Box 92:2115)
    - New Perspectives Quarterly, vol. 6 no. 1, 1989 Spring (Box 92:2116)
    - Proceedings (Institute of Politics), 1977-1979 (Box 92:2117)
    - The Public Perspective, vol. 1 no. 5, 1990 Jul/Aug (Box 92:2118)
    - ReVISION, The Journal of Consciousness and Change, vol. 7, no. 2, 1984/1985 (Box 92:2119)
  - National Commission on Public Service, 1984-1985 (Box 92:2120-2121)
  - New York University
    - Correspondence, 1971, 1975 (Box 93:2122-2123)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1969-1975 (Box 93:2124)
    - Myerson, Paul: untitled paper on hysteric behavior, [1968] (Box 93:2125)
    - "New Way Center - A Program for Troubled Youth", 1971 Feb (Box 93:2126)
    - Notes, 1971 (Box 93:2127)
    - Outreach Program for Runaway and Nomadic Minors: progress report, 1970 (Box 93:2128)
    - "Proposal for an Experimental Street-Level Center Serving the Maturational Needs of Nomadic Minors in New York City", 1969 Dec (Box 93:2129)
    - Psychological Services Center, 1972 (Box 93:2130)
    - "Topics for a Conference on the Legal Status of Minors in the State of New York", 1971 Jan (Box 93:2131)
  - Papers
    - Etzioni, Amatai, "The Two-Track Society", 1982 Jun (Box 93:2132)
    - Mamardashviv, M.K., "The Problem of Consciousness and the Philosopher's Calling", 1988 (Box 93:2133)
    - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, "Children and Welfare Reform", 1981 Jan (Box 93:2134)
    - Project on the Federal Social Role, "Working Paper 4: Social Security", 1985 (Box 93:2135)
    - Project on the Federal Social Role, "Working Paper 5: Medicare", 1985 (Box 93:2136)
    - Schneider, William, "The Public View of the Economy and the Media: What the Polls Show", 1984 (Box 93:2137)
    - Warren, Donald, "White Anger: Middle Americans as a Displaced Majority" - draft, [1989] (Box 93:2138)
  - Presentations and speeches
    - Beck, Bob, "Entitlement and Government Budget", 1984 Jun 11 (Box 93:2139)
    - Cleveland, Harlan, "After Affluence, What?", 1977 Jul 21 (Box 93:2140)
    - Lear, Norman, "America is Strangling on its Obsession with the Bottom Line", 1981 Mar 26 (Box 93:2141)
  - Personal papers
    - Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 93:2142)
    - Reprint scrapbook, 1959-1969 (Box 93:2143)
    - Reprint scrapbook, 1959-1969 (Box 94:2144)
  - Reports
    - Domestic Policy Association
      - (SEE ALSO: boxes 68-69)
      - A Report on the 1984 Forums, 1985 (Box 94:2145)
      - Immigration: What We Promised, Where to Draw the Line, 1986 (Box 94:2146)
  - The Responsive Community, 1991 (Box 94:2147)
  - Russian Federation: surveys on foreign investment, 1992 (Box 94:2148)
  - Russian language: audio tapes, [1992] (Box 94:2149)
  - Survey of high school and college student lifestyles
    - Interviewer instructions, 1974 (Box 94:2150)
    - Survey questions, 1974 (Box 94:2151)
    - Survey forms, 1974 (Box 94:2152)
  - Television series
    - "Choices with Daniel Yankelovich": proposal, 1986 (Box 94:2153)
    - "The Nuclear Age": proposal, 1984 (Box 94:2154)
  - New York Times/CBS Poll: articles, 1980 (Box 94:2155-2156)
  - Tucson Issues Forum, The Homeless: booklet, [1986] (Box 91:2157)
  - Salter, John F., "Shadow Forks: A Small Community's Relationship To Ecology and Regulation, University of California-Santa Cruz Ph.D. dissertation (unboxed), 1981 (Box 94:2157)
- Series VI: Mary Komarnicki Yankelovich,1937-1993
  - Subseries A: Projects, undated, 1937-1991
    - "The Changing Social Contract", [1983] (Box 95:2158)
    - Coming To Public Judgment: Making Democracy Work in a Complex World, 1991
      - (SEE ALSO: boxes 1-12)
      - Research Material
        - Ladd, Carl Everett, The American Polity: The People and Their Government, 1985 (Box 95:2159)
        - O'Dell, Carla, Major Findings From People, Performance, and Pay (photocopy), 1986 (Box 95:2160)
        - Public Opinion Quarterly: articles and book reviews, undated, 1988-1989 (Box 95:2161)
        - Statistic Files
          - AIDS, 1988 (Box 95:2162)
          - American exceptionalism, 1976-1982 (Box 95:2163)
          - Arms control agreements and cheating, 1985-1987 (Box 95:2164)
          - Arms race, 1987-1988 (Box 95:2165)
          - Babyboom generation - values, 1986 (Box 95:2166)
          - Child abuse, 1981-1985 (Box 95:2167)
          - CIA - covert actions, 1973-1986 (Box 95:2168)
          - Cigarette smoking, 1969-1989 (Box 95:2169)
          - Colonel Oliver North, 1987 (Box 95:2170)
          - Communism takeover versus war threat, 1985-1986 (Box 95:2171)
          - Covert actions, 1984 (Box 95:2172)
          - Crime, 1986-1987 (Box 95:2173)
          - Dealing with the Soviets, 1986-1988 (Box 95:2174)
          - Defense spending, 1969-1975 (Box 95:2175)
          - El Salvador, 1981-1986 (Box 95:2176)
          - Environment, 1970-1989 (Box 95:2177)
          - Farming issues, 1945-1985 (Box 95:2178)
          - Flight 007, Korean airline incident, 1983 (Box 95:2179)
          - Homelessness, 1982-1988 (Box 95:2180)
          - Hostages - Iran, 1979-1980 (Box 95:2181)
          - Impact of religious, political and economic freedoms, 1984-1987 (Box 95:2182)
          - Increased defense spending, 1979-1980 (Box 95:2183)
          - Misconceptions of nuclear weapons use, 1982-1985 (Box 96:2184)
          - Mushy areas relating to DPA issues book on U.S.- Soviet relations, 1984-1985 (Box 96:2185)
          - Miscellaneous, 1948-1989 (Box 96:2186)
          - Noriega, Manuel/drug trafficking, 1988 (Box 96:2187)
          - Norms versus behavior, 1986 (Box 96:2188)
          - Nuclear energy, 1986-1989 (Box 96:2189)
          - Nuclear war, 1982-1987 (Box 96:2190)
          - Poland, 1956-1984 (Box 96:2191)
          - Presidential elections, 1984-1988 (Box 96:2192)
          - Probability of having to fight communism/Soviet expansion versus live-and-let-live, 1984-1985 (Box 96:2193)
          - Quest for power and influence - economic, 1987 (Box 96:2194)
          - Quest for power and influence - general, 1987-1988 (Box 96:2195)
          - Quest for power and influence - military, 1986 (Box 96:2196)
          - Safety - survival of a people and a nation, 1979-1986 (Box 96:2197)
          - Soviet intent - expansion versus peace, 1985-1988 (Box 96:2198)
          - Soviet invasion of Afghanistan, 1980 (Box 96:2199)
          - Strategic Defense Initiative (SDI), 1985-1987 (Box 96:2200)
          - Surrogate parenthood, 1987 (Box 96:2201)
          - Terrorism, 1985-1986 (Box 96:2202)
          - Using troops to stop communism versus other measures, 1984-1986 (Box 96:2203)
          - Using troops to stop communism versus other measures, 1937-1987 (Box 96:2204)
          - Work, 1984-1989 (Box 96:2205)
        - The Roper Center for Public Opinion Research, "U.S. Public Opinion on the Gulf Crisis: The Story in Stages", 1990 (Box 96:2206)
        - Vital Speeches of the Day, vol. LII, no. 8, 1986 Feb 1 (Box 96:2207)
      - Notes
        - Chapters 21-23, 1989 (Box 96:2208)
        - Flight 007, savings, and AIDS, 1983-1989 (Box 96:2209)
        - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 96:2210)
      - Search for examples, 1989 (Box 96:2211)
      - Obstacle lists and examples, 1988 (Box 96:2212)
      - Outline: draft B, 1988 Jun 15 (Box 96:2213)
      - Outline: part II, 1988 Jun 15 (Box 96:2214)
      - Outline: draft C, 1988 oct 3 (Box 96:2215)
      - Outline: version D, 1989 Jun 26 (Box 96:2216)
      - Typescript draft/notes: chapter 3, "A Cultural Misunderstanding", 1988 Apr (Box 96:2217)
      - Typescript draft B
        - Chapter 1, "The Quality of Public Opinion", 1988 Apr 7 (Box 96:2218)
        - Chapter 2, "Why the Urgency?", 1988 Apr 20 (Box 96:2219)
        - Chapter 3, "A Cultural Misunderstanding", 1988 Apr 26 (Box 96:2220)
        - Chapter 4, "Three Stages To Public Judgment", 1988 Apr 26 (Box 96:2221)
      - Typescript draft C
        - Introduction, 1989 Feb 14 (Box 96:2222)
        - Introduction, 1989 Feb 17 (Box 96:2223)
        - Chapter C1 "A Missing Concept", [1988] Sep 20 (Box 96:2224)
        - Chapter C2ZZ "How I Encountered It", [1988] (Box 96:2225)
        - Chapter C3 "Searching for Judgment", 1988 Oct 4 (Box 96:2226)
        - Chapter 4 "Judging as Knowing", 1988 Dec 7 (Box 96:2227)
      - Typescript draft D, edited